anadea.info 2019-07-03

# Privacy Statement & Terms of Use - Anadea

By using this website or any other websites and apps owned and operated by Anadea, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Statement.

## Introduction

Anadea values the privacy and security of the information you share with us. The following Privacy Statement is addressed to both companies and individuals who are on this website or interacting with all Anadea services, websites, or apps. This Privacy Statement applies to information collected through anadea.info ("the website"), and information collected through our App cost calculator and Business name generator. This Statement describes how Anadea collects, uses, shares, protects, or otherwise processes your personal information.

IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT, YOU MUST IMMEDIATELY STOP USING THIS WEBSITE AND ALL ANADEA SERVICES.

## Collection and use of information

Anadea collects personal information as required to provide quotes for the provision of services to Clients, and occasionally for marketing and sales campaigns. You may need to provide Anadea with personal information such as:

  * Name;
  * Email address;
  * Mailing address (usually your company’s address);
  * Phone number;
  * Payment details (bank or credit/debit card details, or third-party service details, such as PayPal);
  * Social media account details.

Anadea can use such information for:

  * potentially and/or starting to work together;
  * creating agreements before we start work on a Client project;
  * processing payments and settlement;
  * measuring, improving, and customizing our services;
  * so we can contact you about our work together;
  * fulfilling other technical, logistical, financial, tax, legal, compliance, administrative, or back office functions.

If personal information is only used for a short period (e.g. for specific marketing campaigns) we may delete it.

## Cookies and website usage records

Anadea collects information related to the use of this website using cookies and analytics. Anadea uses cookies to authenticate users when they visit the website, track their session, deliver content specific to their preferences and interests, and provide other functions.

Website log and usage information may include web requests, Internet Protocol address, operating system, browser type, browser language, date and time of the request, and cookies that may uniquely identify the browser and/or device you are using. Anadea uses this information to enhance the functionality of the website and to make access more convenient, secure, and efficient.

Anadea also uses information gathered from logs and cookies to monitor website performance, improve website design, functionality, and security, assemble web analytics and activity trends. Anadea retains such information for as long as reasonably required for business purposes or as reasonably required to comply with our legal obligations.

It is likely that the default setting for your browser is set to automatically accept cookies. You can, however, choose not to accept cookies through your browser controls, by going to the "Tools" or "Preferences" menu. If you would like to learn a little more about changing your browser settings and specifically what cookies are and how they are used look at your browser's help section, FAQ's or click on the following link: [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)

## Data protection

Anadea is committed to taking commercially reasonable steps to protect all of the data we collect, process and use for customers and web visitors. Data is protected in accordance with the **General Data Protection Regulation** ((EU) 2016/679 2018), which came into effect on 25 May 2018. Its purpose is to provide a better understanding to all EU citizens of how their data is being used and to protect the rights and privacy of individuals.

Anadea will not sell, trade or share information to outside third parties. This includes trusted partners or suppliers that we collaborate with, and have a commercial relationship with, and we will assure that they will take measures to protect and keep the data confidential in accordance with GDPR.

## Disclosure of information

Anadea may disclose personal information where:

  * required by law or by an order or requirement of a court, administrative agency, or other government entity, or by court rules concerning the production of records;
  * Anadea has reasonable grounds to believe that use or disclosure is necessary to protect the rights, privacy, property, or safety of other web visitors, other clients, social media users, or any other persons or organisations connected to Anadea;
  * Anadea has reasonable grounds to believe that the information relates to the breach of an agreement or violation of the law that has been, is being, or is about to be committed;
  * it is necessary for fraud protection, risk reduction, or the establishment or collection of funds owed to us;
  * it is necessary to enforce or apply our legal agreements, to pursue remedies, or to limit damages to Anadea;
  * the information is public, which means it is not protected under GDPR and no right to privacy exists;
  * a user has provided consent or with user's direction;
  * other reasons allow it or other laws require it.

When we are required or permitted to disclose information, we will not disclose more information than is necessary to fulfil the disclosure purpose.

Anadea may disclose aggregate or statistical information to our business partners, for public relations purposes, or other purposes.

## Security

Anadea combines technical and physical safeguards with employee policies and procedures to protect user information. We work to protect personal information during transmission by using SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) software, which encrypts the information that is provided online at our Platform. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to protect the information. We will also continue to explore new technology for protecting information and upgrade our information security systems when appropriate.

Further, we permit only authorized Anadea employees to access any personal information. If an employee misuses personal information, we may take disciplinary action, up to and including termination of employment. If any third party individual or organization misuses personal information, we will take action, up to and including termination of any agreement between Anadea and that individual or organization.

## Data integrity

Anadea processes personal information only for the purposes it was originally collected and in accordance with this Privacy Statement. Anadea takes commercially reasonable steps to ensure that the personal data is relevant, reliable for its intended use, accurate, complete, and current for the purposes for which it is used. Anadea retains information for as long as reasonably required for business purposes or as reasonably required to comply with our legal obligations.

## Changes to our Privacy Statement

In the future, if we make any changes to our Privacy Statement we will update this page on our website, so please make sure to check our website and this Privacy Statement periodically.

## In the event of a data breach

We care about our customers and your personal information is our responsibility. To protect your data, our policy will detect any attacks and we will take a responsive action as soon as possible, and as part of that, we will contact you. In compliance with GDPR, if there is a breach we will notify the United Kingdom's Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO), or another EU data protection regulatory body - depending on the jurisdiction where the data breach occurred, or the EU countries where clients or web visitors were affected, within 72 hours of becoming aware of it.

## Contact information

If you have questions or concerns related to this Privacy Statement, please [contact us](https://anadea.info/contacts).

If you would like to know more about the data we have, you have the right to require a copy of the data we hold about you. To check this information, please [contact us](https://anadea.info/contacts).

If you no longer want to appear in our records, we will make sure we to remove you from our database.

For any complaints or concerns about how we manage your personal data, you can [contact us](https://anadea.info/contacts).

## Legal

For legal purposes, "Anadea" and all associated services, websites and apps, are the legal property of Anadea Inc., a Company registered in accordance with the laws of the State of Nevada and the United States of America, and our office is registered at 7848 W. Sahara Avenue, Las Vegas, Nevada, 89117, USA.

If you have questions or concerns related to this Privacy Statement, please [contact us](https://anadea.info/contacts).

By using the Anadea Inc. website or any other websites and apps owned and operated by Anadea, you agree to these Terms of Use. Please read them carefully. If you have any questions, please [contact us](https://anadea.info/contacts).

ACCEPTANCE OF TERMS OF USE

Anadea Inc. ("Anadea"; also, "the Company", "we" or "us" or "our") owns and operates the website anadea.info and any sites and apps we have now or will have in the future reference these Terms of Use (collectively, "Platform").

By using the website or any other websites and apps owned and operated by Anadea, you agree to these Terms of Use and our Privacy Statement.

IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS OF USE, YOU MUST IMMEDIATELY STOP USING THIS WEBSITE AND ALL ANADEA SERVICES.

## Ownership of the website and content

This website, any content on the website and the infrastructure used to provide this website and associated services and social media accounts belongs to Anadea. By using this website and accepting these Terms of Use: Anadea grants you a limited and revocable license to use the website and associated services, such as our App cost calculator and Business name generator, according to these Terms of Use; you agree not to reproduce, distribute, sell or re-sell any content, software or services obtained through the website without express permission from Anadea.

## Access to the website

Anadea reserves the right to deny service or use of this website and associated services to anyone at any time and for any reason. While we use reasonable efforts to keep the website accessible, the website may be unavailable from time to time. You understand and agree that there may be interruptions in Anadea services and website due to circumstances both within our control (e.g., routine maintenance) and outside of our control (e.g., datacenter fault).

## Unauthorized activity

All interactions on this website must comply with these Terms of Use.

The following activities are prohibited on this website and constitute express violations of these Terms of Use:

  1. Submitting any content to this website that:

  * Violates applicable laws (including but not limited to intellectual property laws, laws relating to rights of privacy and rights of publicity and laws related to defamation);
  * Contains viruses or malware;
  * Offers unauthorized downloads of any copyrighted, confidential or private information;
  * Has the effect of impersonating others;
  * Is purposely inaccurate, commits fraud or falsifies information;
  * Is protected by copyright, trademark or another proprietary right without the express permission of the owner of the copyright, trademark or another proprietary right.

  2. Attempting to do or actually doing any of the following on this website:

  * Acting illegally or maliciously against the business interests or reputation of Anadea and our services;
  * Other fraudulent activity on this website or against Anadea.

## Payments and refund policy

Unless otherwise stated, acceptance of these Terms of Use and the use of this website do not constitute, in any way, in any jurisdiction, state or region, an agreement to purchase any services Anadea offers to Clients. Our payments policy, payment terms and refunds policies are all clearly stated when a Client agrees to work with the Company.

## Data protection

Anadea is committed to taking commercially reasonable steps to protect all of the data we collect, process and use for customers and web visitors. Data is protected in accordance with the **General Data Protection Regulation** ((EU) 2016/679 2018), which came into effect on 25 May 2018. Its purpose is to provide a better understanding to all EU citizens of how their data is being used and to protect the rights and privacy of individuals.

Anadea combines technical and physical safeguards with employee policies and procedures to protect user information. We work to protect personal information during transmission by using SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) software, which encrypts the information that is provided online at our Platform. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to protect the information. We will also continue to explore new technology for protecting information and upgrade our information security systems when appropriate.

Anadea will not sell, trade or share information to outside third parties. This includes trusted partners or suppliers that we collaborate with, and have a commercial relationship with, and we will assure that they will take measures to protect and keep the data confidential in accordance with GDPR.

For more information, please see our Privacy Statement above.

## Legal

For legal purposes, "Anadea" and all associated services, websites and apps, are the legal property of Anadea Inc., a Company registered in accordance with the laws of the State of Nevada and the United States of America, and our office is registered at 7848 W. Sahara Avenue, Las Vegas, Nevada, 89117, USA.

If you have questions or concerns related to these Terms of Use, please [contact us](https://anadea.info/contacts).
